Today we come to this place
the se
The Za.
Can you see it?
How do I get this on film?
Can you see me?
Here we are at Ste World.
I knew it.
I did it!
Ai got it for me.
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy!
You know, your hair band is amazing.
It's so colorful.
There's so many.
I've been wanting to go there for a long time.
I've been looking at the vlogs and stuff, and it comes up a lot.
I'm looking forward to the day when you can go.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to have fun.
I'm going to go!
I'll be there.
I'll pick the most popular one.
Oh, wait, there's a ranking.
Oh, wow.
This is the most popular.
This is...This is...
But it could be pretty.
There's pink, too.
Oh, really?
I'll put the most popular one on.
Most popular.
It's cute.
It's adorable. It's so adorable.
Really? Really?
It fits.
I can see you in it.
She's cute.
It's cute.
I thought it was a jellyfish, but is it an octopus?
An octopus?
There's so many different kinds.
It's fun.
Oh, my God. I have to decide.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This one's cute.
The one with the dangling strawberries.
It's so cute!
It goes with everything.
I like it.
Do you think there's something on it?
What's that? What is it?
Strawberry bean jam.
I think I can eat it.Looks edible.
It's so cute!
You don't see many of these in Japan.
The one with the handle.
It's cute. Is that a different color?
It looks really good on you.
It's cute.
I like this one.
It's definitely a good one.
It's adorable.
Here.
Cute.
Let's put a thimper on it with this guy.
Suddenly it all comes together.
Suddenly.
We're here.
We were trying to get here.
Yes, so we went inside.
Oh, my God! We all did. We even picked out matching catsuits.
Matching ones in different colors.
It was hard to decide, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was a bit of a maze!
It's really exciting just to walk around inside!
It's so big, so big!
It's not enough!
I'm outside right now.
It took me so long to get out!
It took me so long!I had so little time!
Amazing!!!!
That's great!
Yes, the best part is, can you see this castle?
I see it!
Oh, it's just an ear!
Oh, it's so cute!
I came outside to see this castle.
Yes, and the walk through was a lot of fun, too.
So much fun!
There were a lot of restaurants that looked delicious.
I think I'm going to go eat after this!
Yay!
Let's down!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy with the different color of these ears!
Cute. Your ears.
You're rocking it.
Cute.
Great. Great.
I heard Ayumi likes MechaDeck. I'm so excited.
I can ride anything. It's awesome.
Great! I'll ride anything you can ride, Fumiko.
Let's all ride together.
I'm not good with the tactile drop stuff.
Like this.
Look, look, look!
Oh, no, no, no, no!Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
What? What's this?
It looks like a sunflower.
It looks like a sunflower toilet.
Let's eat something.
Let's eat.
Wow! There's so many!
Oranges!
Chilos!
Did they get away?
I want some chilos!
Let's eat some chilos!
I found the chilos you wanted.
I'm so glad you said you wanted chilos!
Labo!
Looks like chilos.
Would you like some chilos?
Would you like to try some?
Am!
Delicious!
Would you like to try some?
It's so cute!
Here you go!
Bon appétit!
Bring it!Bring it!
I want to hold it.
I have a sushi tongue!
No, you don't!
Spoil him!
I'll indulge you now!
First things first!
Be pampered!
Owners!
Bon appétit!
Ah!
Yes!
So we got chilos!
Yay!
Delicious!
I wanted to be made, today.
I'm so happy.
What did you say about "Itadakimasu"?
What is it? Itadakimasu?
I looked it up!
What?
That's it!
Chalmokkesumu nida!
Chalmokkeesmeunida?
Ready!
Chalmokkeesumu nida!
Ah!
Please!Please!
Hmm? Yes!
o
niinichentle
улиz pu 태태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태 or 태.
There's a mouse!
Is this it?
Yes!
French Revolution!
I got it!
I got a ride!
It's fun! Let's ride!
How long is the wait?
There are so many mazes!
Maybe this is what you get at Magic Pasta.
I'll have one!
This other one looks delicious!
I think we could go together.
What?
French Revolution tickets.
Oh, what?
Sold out?
No, they're not.
You have time.
Bye-bye.
He said bye-bye.
It's amazing, but I'm so glad I finally got this shot.It's amazing, but I'm glad I finally got it.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's like a father and son.
Yay!
Long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long.
Long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long, long.
We did it!
That was fun!
It was bitter and long and I was spinning for the rest of my life.
That's great!
I was able to ride it.
I got to ride a new session.
It was peaceful!
Then yay for being able to make custom phone cases now!
So cute.
There are so many of them.
I would like to make my original phone case
Yay!
That's great!
What's your phone model like that?
I'm 11.
14 pro.
That's what I'm talking about.
Mr. Daisen, 15 Pro.
Senpai.
Wait a minute.
This is Ivon, too.
Decals.Decals.
Decals. Decals.
Eleven.
They're not black.
It's just black.
What's this?
Black.
It's not black.
Not black?
I don't know.
I got 11.
There's a lot of them here.
There's something in here, too.
There's so many of them.
There's so many!
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute, this is fun.
It's fun.
What's this?
Combine it with this.
Awesome.
It's so cute.
There's even a bunny.
I kind of like the string.I kinda like the string.
I like the string.
I love it.
Awesome!
That's so cute.
Cute.
Yes, ma'am.
Hi, I'm Sheepdashi from Stay World.
That was a lot of fun.
Yeah, it was.
And winter.
I wanted to ride more, but there was a lot of attractions and stuff.
It was difficult.
Yeah.
I want to go again.
I'd like to go again.
I have a great memory.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
See you soon!
Yes, I went to Lotte World, and I went to a store where you can customize a lot of phone cases.
I would like to introduce my purchases.I would like to introduce my purchase.
That's right. I didn't.
Moe, please.
I got lost on the way back.
I got a black iPhone case and a key chain with heart hardware.
It's so cute!
A bunny and a cute little bunny!
I fell in love at first sight.
I'll give you lots of blouses
The last one is the new year's daughter!
You're a senior woman!
It's the mob.
Yearling bunny.
I'm a 14 year old.
This little bunny...
She's so cute!
I'm the oldest daughter.
We're the same.
I love the way she's got her face all hunched up.
So cute!
I chose this one.
I chose this glittery one.
Like this on the side.
Hey, it's full of beads.
So cute!
I chose this one because I thought it would be really cute if it sparkled like this.
It's so nice and simple, but gorgeous!Very nice, simple but gorgeous!
Yay!
I wonder if I can get a photo card of my favorite member's In Mitsu.
Miyajun-chan has a photo card, too...
I'll put it in!
Yes!
You're right, Sayan.
You look a little like her.
You're showing it so much!
I just showed it for the first time.
I just showed you so much.
He's so cute!
I'm so happy.
Wait, I should've done that too.
I should've gone with the clear one.
It's so cute.
Yes, I have this clear one.
I wanted to put a card or something in it, too.
I got this one in Vienna.
This flower...
Cute!
I love the word "smile" because it says "smiley face".
I thought this one was very cute, too.
It's simple.
I like to put them on my phone.
That's right.
So I decided to do this simple one.So I made this simple one.
I'm so glad you thought to put something like this in there.
Oh, my God, that's great.
I'm so happy for you.
It's amazing.
It's amazing that he eats like this.
It's just... it's just...
Amazing.
You did it!
It's so great!
I can see the difference here.
It's true.
It's got flowers in it.
What?
It's so cute!
It's really cute.
I really enjoyed it.
Thank you so much.
I have a lot of memories of you.
I'll use them all in Japan!
If you've been there...
If you are going...
I'd be happy to share them with you.
I look forward to working with you.
Bye bye!